┵



Nikolaiev Mykhailo

Full Stack developer

O Ukraine, Kyiv

☑ ab3mn3@gmail.com

& +38-066-800-79-85

SOCIAL

in in/mykhailo-nikolaiev

ab3MN

</>

Codewars

EDUCATION

Thermal power engineer

Kyiv energy college

2006-2010

Thermal power engineer

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

2014-2018

COURSE

JavaScript/Front-end Pre-school

RS School

Jun 2023- November 2023

JavaScript/Front-end

RS School

Nov 2023 - Jun 2024

$\textbf{S}\,\textbf{K}\,\textbf{I}\,\textbf{L}\,\textbf{L}\,\textbf{S}$

• HTML/Markdown • CSS/SCSS

• JavaScript • TypeScript

ReactRedux/Zustand

• GIT/GitHub • REST/WebSocket

• Clean Code • SOLID & PATTERNS

SOFT SKILLS

• Documentation • Communicative

• Team Player • Creative

• Detailed • Adaptable

PROFILE

6

A goal-oriented Entry Level Frontend Developer with knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Type Script and React seeking to use technical proficiency and creativity to develop engaging user experiences and advance in a professional career. Looking to leverage effective debugging, code optimization and project collaboration capabilities to produce applications that exceed user expectations.

My current main goal is speak English fluently like a native speaker, find the first job in the IT field and become a middle within one years.

EXPERIENCE

Warehouse manager

From 2021 to Present | PLV SYSTEMS

Storekeeper

From 2018 to 2019 | Kasta

Mechanic engineer of machine manufacturer

From 2014 to 2018 | Kyiv Electric Train Repair Plant

PORTFOLIO

Coffee-House: HTML/SCSS/Java Script

Hangman: HTML/SCSS/JavaScript

Nonograms: HTML/SCSS/JavaScript

Online Store: React/TS/ZUSTAND/MUi/Commercetools

Clean Code: Refactoring else's code

Refactor bad code

Html Builder: Create a small console utility working with files

Need to download

Plv: React/TypeScript/SCSS

LANGUAGES

Ukraine
 Russian
 English B1-B2(in process)

INTERESTS

	*	
Music	Travel	Book
(H)	ů	*
Gvm	Study	Walk